https://stbedesmentonetigers.com.au/our-policy/privacy/

Supporter Membership
Senior Membership (VAFA)
Junior Membership (SMJFL)
Supporter Membership
Senior Membership (VAFA)
Junior Membership (SMJFL)
Breaking News
Welcome To Our Brand New Website!The new facilities are fantastic.Really looking forward to season 2021.Social distancing saves lives.
St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC > Our Policy > Privacy
MissionCode of ConductChild SafeVilificationAlcohol ManagementIllegal Drug UseSmoke FreePrivacyTerms Of Use
Privacy Statement
The St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC is committed to the protection of your personal information. The following explains how your personal information will be treated as you access and interact with the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC web site. In knowing this you are then able to make knowledgeable choices about whether to provide personally identifiable information to us and to give you the opportunity to direct us to limit the manner in which your personally identifiable information is used.
The St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC fully supports the National Privacy Principles for the Fair Handling of Personal Information and will continually review and update our privacy policies as appropriate, hence we encourage you to check our online privacy Statement regularly.
Data Collection
The information that we will collect about you will depend on how you use the facilities offered by the web site. For example, when completing a membership application we will collect details such as name, surname, address, email address, date of birth, contact number, etc. Some of this information is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service and as such is mandatory. Other types of information are collected to help us profile who is using the services and what their interests are. Information of this type is often optional, however when provided enables us to continually ensure our products and services reflect the changing interests of our customers.
Data Usage
The personally identifiable information that we collect through this web site is initially used to satisfy you with the service requested. We also gather and analyse personally identifiable information that we have collected from this web site to enable us to develop marketing programs and service offerings tailored to the relevant customer base.
The St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC may also use your personal information for the purpose of direct marketing in relation to promotional activities where it is impracticable for us to obtain your prior consent. When this is done, we will provide an opportunity when we first contact you to decline receiving any further marketing communications from the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC, via an opt-out mechanism.
Data Disclosure
Personal information that you submit on our website is stored on the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC’s database. The Club will not sell or otherwise disclose this information to any unrelated third party. It may be used for the purpose of direct marketing in relation to promotional activities of the St Bedes / Mentone Tigers AFC or in conjunction with a major sponsor where it is impracticable for us to obtain your prior consent. Such promotions will be run by the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC on behalf of the particular club sponsor. When this is done, we will provide an opportunity when we first contact you to decline receiving any further marketing communications from the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC, via an opt-out mechanism.
Data Security
The St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC will take reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up to date and stored in a secure environment accessed only by authorised persons.
Data Access
You have a right of access to personally identifiable information held by the St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC about you. If at anytime you wish to review or make corrections to your personal information held, you are able to do this by using the customer profile icon located on the website, or by contacting the Club via email at club@stbedesmentonetigers.com.au
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Consent
If you decide to contribute your personal information to this web site, you consent to our collecting, using, disclosing and retaining that personal information as set out in this Statement or otherwise permitted under the National Privacy Principles, until such time as you request us to stop using or disclosing that information.
How to Contact us
The St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC welcomes any feedback you may have regarding our privacy policy. If you have any questions or queries please send us an email.
PO Box 417, Mentone, VIC 3194club@stbedesmentonetigers.com.auQuick LinksNews
Stay current with our latest news.
Copyright © 2020 St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC. All Rights Reserved.
Copyright © 2020 St Bedes/Mentone Tigers AFC. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy | Terms of Use
Follow Us:
Privacy | Terms of Use
